A Guide to the John M. Sherwood Collection, circa 1860-2011
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 3: Oversize, 1920-1983
  - Mail order house plans, undated (Drawer 3, Folder 4)
  - Large plans, plats, 1941-1966 (Drawer 4)
  - Plans for Albert Sherwood residence and unknown basement plan, circa 1936 (Folder 5)
  - Large plans, plats, 1931-1950 (Folder 6)
  - Albert Sherwood residence elevations, circa 1936
- Series 4: Realia, 1868-1980
  - Personal photograph album, John Sherwood, circa 1937-1941 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Road sign, "Kamp Washington Fairfax VA", circa 1930-1960 (Drawer 5, Folder 1)
  - Oval frame with glass dome, 1875 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Wedding photograph, Savilla C. and Henry S. Myers, 1875 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Oval frame with glass dome, 1913 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Wedding photograph, Annie B. and Albert R. Sherwood, 1913 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Women's shoes, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Petrified Wood found at Tyson's Corner, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Leather Wallet "Valuable Papers", Fussell-Young Ice Cream Co., Washington, DC, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Book of hymns and texts, inscribed "Savila Stotelmeyer her book September 6, 1868", 1868 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Frisbee, George Mason Bank, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Small People's Drug Box, labeled "Pictures of houses just before moving Mar. 20, 1967", 1967 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Leather keychain, George Mason Bank, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Zippo key holder, Fairfax Furniture Company, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Pinback button, Hot B-106.7 FM, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Pencil, The Dura-Wear Company, George W. Hurley, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Certificate for perfect attendance, Albert Maurice Sherwood, Oakton High School, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - $10 note, National Bank of Fairfax, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Wooden gasoline gauge, Tyson's Corner Garage, circa 1920-1929 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Car license tax tag, Fairfax, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Newspaper clipping regarding pertified wood found at Tyson's Corner, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Group photograph, Oakton High School graduating class of 1934, including Albert Maurice Sherwood, 1934 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - John M. Sherwood, Methodist Sunday school promotion certificate, 1923 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Invoice, Murphy and Ames Lumber Dealers, Rosslyn, Virginia, 1936 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Golf towel, George Mason Bank, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Spanish silver coin found when well dug near Sherwood home in 1920s, Main St., Fairfax, circa 1920-1930 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Memo pad, George Mason Bank, undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Rent receipt book, Kamp Washington property, 1965-1966 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Leather letter case, C. Elmer Parker, Clarendon, undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Dime bank, Vienna Trust Co., undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Class ring and receipt for payment, John M. Sherwood, Fairfax High School, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Checkbook cover, George Mason Bank, undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Unknown advertising item, Fairfax Furniture Co., undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Paperweight, George Mason Bank, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Advertising fan (?), H.S. Myers, Falls Church, undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Metal sign, H.S. Myers, Tyson's Crossroads (1 of 2), undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Metal sign, H.S. Myers, Tyson's Crossroads (2 of 2), undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Pencils, George Mason Bank, undated (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Guest ledger, Sherwood's Tourist Home, 1928-1951 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Household accounts ledger, Sherwood family, 1953-1958 (Box 22, Folder 2)